

CARLO RUGGIERO

California Polytechnic University
San Luis Obispo, CA

PROFILE

I am a third year at California Polytechnic University studying for a Bachelors of Computer Science. Throughout my work experience and time at Cal Poly, I have developed valuable leadership skills and a strong work ethic across a variety of settings.

SKILLS

Languages

Java, C, JavaScript, Python, RISCV/MIPS,

Skills

Data structures, operating systems, computer architecture

CHARACTER REFERENCES

Garry Osmond

Track and Field Coach, Bainbridge High School Cell: 206-790-5110

Jordan Pitre

Assistant General Manager, Wing Point GCC Cell: 206-842-2688

CONTACT INFO

Cell: 206-823-9094

Email: ruggicar555@gmail.com

WORK EXPERIENCE

Server's Assistant, Wing Point GCC

August 2018 - September 2019

- Member of the waitstaff at the Wing Point Golf and Country Club
- Served and bused tables for the restaurant
- Hosted parties, weddings, and other events, providing catering and organizational assistance

Camp Counselor, Bainbridge Island

June 2019 - July 2019

- Worked as a camp counselor for Bainbridge Island Parks and Rec's running camp
- Coached proper running skills along with health and fitness tips
- Worked with kids of all ages, providing help with organization and leadership

EDUCATION

Bainbridge High School, WA

September 2015 - June 2019

- Graduated with a 3.9 unweighted GPA
- Member of the National Honor Society

California Polytechnic University, CA

September 2019 - Present

- Studying for a Bachelors of Science in Computer Science, with a minor in marketing and communications
- Competing on the Track and Field team for Cal Poly at the Division I level